{
	"1": {
 		"question": "How many oscars did the Titanic movie got?",
 		"answer": "11"
 	},
 	"2": {
 		"question": "What is the house number of the Simpsons?",
 		"answer": "742"
 	},
 	"3": {
 		"question": "What is the name of the little dragon in the animated movie Mulan?",
 		"answer": "Mushu"
 	},
 	"4": {
 		"question": "How long is the Great Wall of China? (miles)",
 		"answer": "4000 miles"
 	},
 	"5": {
 		"question": "How many stars does the American flag have?",
 		"answer": "50"
 	},
 	"6": {
 		"question": "A Chital is a species of which hooved mammal?",
 		"answer": "deer"
 	},
 	"7": {
 		"question": "How many feet are in a fathom?",
 		"answer": "6"
 	},
 	"8": {
 		"question": "Which character from the pen of Bram Stoker, was first made into a film in 1931?",
 		"answer": "Dracula"
 	},
 	"9": {
 		"question": "On Halloween, if a black cat crosses your path, what will you receive?",
 		"answer": "bad luck"
 	},
 	"10": {
 		"question": "Which film has as its main characters, Morticia and Gomez?",
 		"answer": "The Addams family"
 	}
 }